# **Christian Franco**

**Nationality:** Spanish **Date of birth:** 09/06/2001 **Phone:** (+34) 626554625

Email: <a href="mailto:christianfrancosoto@gmail.com">christianfrancosoto@gmail.com</a>

in LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/christian-franco-soto/

**Website:** christianfranco.dev

• Home: (Spain)

#### **ABOUT MYSELF**

I'm a full-stack developer with a strong focus on back-end and solid knowledge in web development, with 3 years of experience in software development. My passion for programming is combined with a desire to learn and improve my knowledge.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

**Idrica** – Spain

Country: Spain

# **Full Stack Developer**

[ 08/2023 - Current ]

Application and REST API development using .Net Core (C#) for the backend and Angular (TypeScript) for the frontend, using SQL Server and PostgreSQL for database management.

I have also contributed in a web application working on the frontend and functionality with React and .Net Core. I have used other tools like Git (GitLab) or Postman.

# **Ⅲ Técnicas Competitivas S.A.** – Spain

Country: Spain

# **Junior Software Developer**

[ 06/2022 - 08/2023 ]

- Development and maintenance of a web application for economic management using C# ASP.NET MVC.
- Development, management and maintenance of a database in SQL Server.
- Working group with Scrum methodology.
- Version control with GitLab.
- Use of other tools: NUnit for testing, SonarQube for code quality, DocFX to generate documentation and Jenkins for continuous integration.

## **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

## Higher Technician in Multi-platform Applications Development

**CIFP César Manrique** [ 09/2020 – 06/2022 ]

Country: Spain

### **LANGUAGE SKILLS**

Mother tongue(s): Spanish
Other language(s): English

### **SKILLS**